[{"answer": "Would you please", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Told me what?", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I did", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I did", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I got you an apartment in the building", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " She died?", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "She died", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "She died", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " She died?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "She died", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "She died", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Get out!  Four hundred a month? Only four hundred a month?", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Four hundred a month", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Right upstairs", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "And I'll be right upstairs", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Right above you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Right upstairs", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Right above me", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Thanks, see ya later, my friend.  What happened to you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What? What did you do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You can't believe what I just did", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I could tell you what I did, but you wouldn't believe it. It's not believable", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What? What did you do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What did you do", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I could tell you what I did, but you wouldn't believe it. It's not believable", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "How could I have done that", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What did you do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Done what", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend's moving into your building", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Right above you", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I know. Neighbors", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Right above me", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "She's right in my building! Right above me! Every time I come in the building, I'm gonna have to sneak around like a cat burglar", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "But I need the home bed advantage", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Religion, my friend, that's what happened to me. Because, I have just been informed that it's going to cost my friend the sum of five thousand dollars to get the apartment upstairs", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Of course she doesn't have five thousand dollars", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Of course she doesn't have five thousand dollars", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Can't get it", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "So, okay. What's the problem", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "C'mon, you can come up with five thousand dollars.. my friend, you don't have five thousand dollars you can led her? Come on", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yeah, so what's the problem", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "He said he'd loan you the money", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Get outta here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Apartment.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What's to think about", "qsentId": 46}]